Addison Eastway

Student, Salesperson

Enterprising, imaginative senior undergraduate student at the Australian National University with a resolute ambition and an entrepreneurial mindset. Extensive experience delivering efficient, personal and profitable customer experiences, methodical collaboration in professional team environments and achieving/surpassing key business targets. A visionary, creative and optimist, with a demonstrated ability to quickly adapt quickly and a fervent passion for learning and self improvement.

Contact

Phone

0412814463

Email

addisoneastway@icloud.com

Address

50 Daley Road, Acton, ACT

Education

2024

Bachelor of Commerce

Australian National University

2021

International Baccalaureate Diploma

Newington College Perfect Score

Expertise

- Swift UI (iOS) Development
- Python
- MS Office
- Apple OS
- POS Systems
- RSA/RCG

Accolades

- Dux of Newington College
- UQ Vice-Chancellor's Scholar
- International Baccalaureate Excellence
- Drummond DC Sales Award x4
- Prefect, House Vice-Captain
- Gold Service Learning Award

Language

English

French

Experience

O 2023 - 2024

Drummond Golf I 16 Goolwa PI, Fyshwick ACT 2609

Sales Assistant

As Australia's premier golf retailer for over 40 years, Drummond Golf has been providing the largest range of the world's leading golf brands at competitive prices to golfers of all levels and ages. From a small store in Bendigo in 1974, today Drummond Golf is Australia's largest off-course golf retailer with 50 stores nationwide.

- Selling golf equipment and all related products.
- Customer service and inquiries.
- Tailored state-of-the-art golf equipment fitting experience.
- · Merchandising of stock in a professional manner.
- Liaising with suppliers regarding stock and customer orders.
- Receiving, storage and replenishing stock on the floor.

2022 - 2023

Strive45 Tutoring I Sydney

Private Tutor

- Strive45 IB tutors are the highest calibre of IB alumni who excelled in the IB with a minimum of 44 (99.85), with 80% having received a perfect score of 45 (99.95 ATAR).
- Our IB tutors only tutor subjects where they received a strong 7 and have demonstrated teaching experience.
- Support is provided using key study skills such as organisation, study habits, note-taking and overall effective study practices.

2024 -

Radio 1RPH | Canberra

Volunteer, Administration and Finance Team

Radio 1RPH is a Community Radio broadcaster based in Canberra. We are an independent, not-for-profit organisation that provides a radio reading service to people with print disabilities as well as to the general listening public.

2022 - 2023

Velluti's Fruit and Veg Company

Store and Warehouse Worker

References

Greg Hood AO

Deputy Chair Airservices Australia Acting Chair CSIRO Marine National Facility Steering Committee Chair Australian Aviation Hall of Fame President Canberra Ovations Awards Director Air Force Association

Phone: +61 418 123 145

Email: greghood@internode.on.net

Yevette Ho

Station Manager, Radio 1RPH

Phone: +61 481 230 391

Email: manager@radio1rph.org.au

Matt Hoole

Store Manager, Drummond Golf Fyshwick

Phone: +61 439 834 034

Steve Muir

Housemaster, Newington College

See Below

Email: contact@newington.nsw.edu.au



December 2021

TESTIMONIAL FOR ADDISON JAMES EASTWAY

To Whom It May Concern

Addison has been a student of Newington since commencing in 2016 in Year 7. He graduated from Year 12 in 2021. In that time, he has shown himself to be an outstanding academic. His awards include PR Le Couteur Prize for Scholarship, Sports and Citizenship (2019), Proxime Accessit (2019), the Holiday Prize for Divinity (2019), Academic Colours (2019), Outstanding Academic Achievement in the International Baccalaureate Diploma Programme in (2020). Addison has sustained high academic achievement throughout his school career and has shown an organised and thorough approach to his studies.

Newington College offers an array of co-curricular opportunities, and Addison has tried many. In the sporting arena, he participated in football, cricket, and golf, displaying great endeavour and commitment. He was the number one ranked player in the competition golf team in 2021. He has been heavily involved in the school's Music program as part of the Symphonic Winds, Wind Orchestra, Stage Band, Rock Band and College Choir, earning Music Colours for his contributions. He participated in the College Musicals in 2016, 2018 and 2020. The wealth of his involvements and subsequent accomplishments are listed in the school participation transcript and serves as a testament to Addison's diverse range of interests and the flexibility of character and outstanding organisation required to maintain such high standards in a broad range of areas.

In his final year, Addison also gained Honour Colours in recognition of his commitment to the College's activities over several years. His contribution to the Outdoor Education Program was rewarded, with Addison being appointed Newington Challenge Captain. His duties included attendance at all annual camps, fulfilling leadership courses and training younger students in a variety of skills.

Addison has always modelled self-respect, excellent communication, and outstanding leadership, typified by his selection into the Year 11 Peer Support program and his appointment as vice-captain of Moulton House. His primary role was to work with the House Captain to prepare duty rosters for a team of over 30 House Prefects, supervise the performance of their duties, prepare a written evaluation of their performance, and liaise with members of the teaching staff. He fulfilled his responsibilities exceptionally well, setting the highest standards of personal conduct, dress and involvement in school activities, and consistently demonstrated empathy and care for students of all ages. Furthermore, his strength of character, willingness to confront difficult situations and find solutions were essential traits exhibited. His service to the school community was much appreciated.

Addison is a truly exceptional young man for whom I have the utmost regard. He has remarkably intrinsic flexibility, organisation and proficiency with prioritising commitments that have been invaluable in ensuring he makes the most of and achieves the best results in whatever he pursues. His maturity, care and thoughtfulness set him apart, and he was well respected by staff and students. He has an inquiring mind and a thirst for continual self-improvement that will ensure he thrives in whatever endeavours he pursues as he leaves Newington. He has our highest recommendation.

Mr Michael Parker Headmaster

Total Och

Mr Steven Muir **Head of House**

200 Stanmore Road, Stanmore NSW 2048 Tel: 02 9568 9333 Fax: 02 9568 9521 STANMORE Email: contact@newington.nsw.edu.au



newington.nsw.edu.au



13 February 2023

To Whom It May Concern,

Reference: Addison Eastway

I have known Addison Eastway for the past two years since he commenced working in our business. His availability to work has been subject to his university commitments and he is an extremely reliable and dedicated worker. Over the recent summer period we have been fortunate to have Addison working at an almost full-time capacity as a warehouse assistant and delivery driver.

Addison is a quick learner, organised and punctual. He demonstrates common sense, is a team player and is very amiable with work colleagues and customers. He is and will be an asset to any organisation and I recommend him highly for any position he applies for.

I would be pleased to provide further information on Addison's employment and can be contacted on 0407 402038.

Yours sincerely,

John Leo Velluti Managing Director

John Velleti